Pelham, Ruth; Papers apap408
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Grant Funding, 1978-2016; 2; 6.0 cubic ft.
  - 1999 Legislative Local Initiative Grant (Senator Joseph Bruno), 1986; 1999-2000; 2006-2007; Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 2004 Albany/Schenectady League of Arts Community, Arts Connection Grant, 1986; 2003-2004; Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 2009/2010 Legislative Initiative Grant Application (Senator Breslin), 1986; Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - The Capital City Fund of the Community Foundation, 1986; 2015 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 1993 Decentralization Plan of the Capital Region Grant, 1986-1987; 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 2001 City of Albany Youth Bureau Grant (1 of 2), 1988; 1990; 1992-1993; 1995-2002; Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 2001 City of Albany Youth Bureau Grant (2 of 2), 1988; 1990; 1992-1993; 1995-2002; Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 1993 Ben and Jerry's Foundation Grant Proposal, 1988; 1993-1994; Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1992 Decentralization Plan for Capital District Grant, 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Local Initiative Grant (Senator J. Bruno), 1990; 1993; 1997-2001; 2003; Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 1992 City of Albany Arts Commission Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 1992, 1993 City of Albany Arts Commission Grant, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - City of Albany Arts Commission Grant Letter Writing Campaign, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Albany Arts Commission-County Initiative Grant, 1991-1992; 1995 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Albany Arts Commission, 1991; 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 1993 City of Albany Arts Grant Application, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Music Mobile Donor List and Correspondence, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 1993 City of Albany Arts Commission Grant, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 1994 Frederick McDonald Trust/Fleet Investment Services, 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 1994 City of Albany Arts Grants Application, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Albany/Schenectady of Arts, Arts Update Vol.V #3, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Articles About Arts Funding in the Capital Region, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - 1997 County of Albany Youth Bureau Grant, 1993-1994; 1996-1997; 1999; Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - McEneny Proposal-93-96 Grant, 1993-1996; Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 1994 CDBG Final Report - Music Mobile's "All Together Now!" Youth Project (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - 1995 Frederick McDonald Trust/Fleet Grant, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Photo Documentation for Final Report of 1994 "All Together Now!" Youth Project (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 1994 CDBG Final Report-Music Mobile's "All Together Now!" Youth Project, Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - 1995 Community Foundation Grant for Van Replacement, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - 1995 Decentralization Plan for the Capital District Grant, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - CDBG 1994 Final Report Photo Documentation, 1994-1995; 1997 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Certification of Merit, 1994-1996; 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - CDBG Final Report Photos, 1994-1997; Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - 1996 City of Albany Arts Grant Application, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - 1996 Frederick Mc Donald Trust/Fleet Grant, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - 95-96 CDBG Final Report, 1995; Undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - 1995-1996 CDBG Final Report-Music Mobile's "All Together Now!" Youth Project (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - East West Planning Notes and Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - 1995/1996 CDBG Final Report - Music Mobile's "All Together Now!" Youth Project, Undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - 1996 Decentralization Plan for the Capital District Grant, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - 95-96 CDBG Report Photos Originals, 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - 1998 Community Arts Connection Application, 1995-1997; Undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - City of Albany Office of Youth and Recreation Grants and Vouchers, 1995-2000; Undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Community Arts Connection Grant/Community Development Block Grant, 1995-2001 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - 96-97 ATN Final Report Color Photos Originals, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - 1997 City of Albany Arts Grant Application, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - 1997 Frederick McDonald Trust, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence for Additional Funding for New Computer, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - 1996-1997 CDBG Final Report - Music Mobile's "All Together Now!" Youth Project (B+W Photos), Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1996-1997 CDBG Final Report - Music Mobile's "All Together Now!" Youth Project (Color Photos), Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1997 Capital District ARTS Decentralization Grant Program, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Community Arts Connection Grant, 1996-2000 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1998 City of Albany Arts Grant Application, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Albany/Schenectady League of Arts, 1997 Arts Awards (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - New York State Assembly Certificate of Merit, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Summer 97 Flyers/Publicity, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Notes from Grant Application Revision Meeting 4/8/97 w/Miki…, 1997; Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 1998 Frederick McDonald Trust, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Albany/Schenectady League of Arts Community Arts Connection Cultural Services Agreement and Congratulations Letter, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Albany/Schenectady League of Arts, Community Arts Connection Grant, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 1998 County of Albany Youth Bureau, 1997-1999; Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 1999 County of Albany Youth Bureau, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 2002 Albany/Schenectady League of Arts, Community Arts Connection Grant, 1997; 2000-2001; Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - 2001 Albany County Youth Bureau Grant, 1997; 2000-2002; Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - 2002 Albany County Youth Bureau Funding Request, 1997; 2001-2003; Undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - 2007 City of Albany Arts Grant Application, 1997; 2001-2002; 2004-2006; Undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - 1999 City of Albany "Act 2000" Grant Application, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - 1998/1999 CDBG Final Report - Music Mobile's "All Together Now!" Youth Project, Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - 1998 Frederick McDonald Trust, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - 1999 Legislative Local Initiative Grant Application (Senator Ronald Canestrari) (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - 2000 City of Albany "Act 2000" Arts Grant Application, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Advantage After - School Grant: Sheri/YMCA/NYS Children and Family Services, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - McEneny 99/00 Legislative Initiative Grant, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - 1999-2000 CDBG Final Report - Music Mobile's "All Together Now!" Youth Project, Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - 1999-2000 CDBG Final Report - Music Mobile's "All Together Now!" Youth Project (B+W Photos), Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - 1999-2000 CDBG Final Report - Music Mobile's "All Together Now!" Youth Project (Color Photos), Undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Notes and Papers for Legislative Local Initiative Grant Application (Senator Neil D. Breslin), 1999-2000; Undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - 2001 Albany/Schenectady League of Arts Community, Arts Connection Grants, 1999-2001 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - The Community Arts Connection, 1999-2001 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - 2000 County of Albany Youth Bureau, 1999-2001; Undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - 2010 Legislative Initiative Grant (Majority Leader Ron Canestrari), 1999; 2001; 2007 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - 2007-2008 Legislative Local Initiative Grant Application Correspondence, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - 2000 Delegation Legislative Initiative Grant - R. Canestrari, P. Tonko, J. McEneny (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - 2000 Legislative Initiative Item Request (Senator J. Bruno) (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - 2001 City of Albany Arts Grants Application, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - McEneny 2000 Legislative Initiative Grant (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - 2000 Legislative Local Initiative Grant Application (Senator Ronald Canestrari), Undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - 2000 Tonko Legislative Initiative Grant, Undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - 2000-2001 Legislative Local Initiative Grant Application (Senator Neil D. Breslin), Undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - CDBG 2000-2001 Final Report, Undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Common Council Presentation 12/00 - Increased Funding for Youth Bureau/Teen Corps, 2000; Undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Winter/Spring 2000 Troy Programs Contract, Undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - 2001 McEneny Legislative Initiative Grant, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - 2000 City Youth Bureau Grant, 2000-2001; Undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - 2002 Albany/Schenectady League of Arts Community Arts Connection Grant, 2000-2001; Undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - "All Together Now!" Youth Project 2000-2001 Photo Documentation, Undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - CDBG 2000 Van Restoration Funds, 2000-2003; Undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - 2002/2003 Albany County Youth Bureau Grants, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Legislative Local Initiative Grant (Assemblyman James Tedisco), 2000-2001; 2007; 2009; Undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - FY 2000-2001 Legislative Member Item Award - Delegation Grant, 2000-2004; Undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - 2002 City of Albany Arts Grant Application, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Tonko 2001 Legislative Initiative Request (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - 2001 Legislative Local Initiative Grant (Assembly Member Ronald Canestrari), Undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - 2001-2002 Legislative Local Initiative Grant Application (Senator Neil D. Breslin), Undated (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - The Albany/Schenectady League of Arts Community Arts Connection 2001 Grant, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - CDBG 2001-2002 Final Report, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 2002 Albany/Schenectady League of Arts Community Arts Connection Grant, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 2001 Albany/Schenectady League of Arts Community Arts Connection Grant Interim Report Final Report, Budget Revision Forms, 2001-2002; Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 2001 City Youth Bureau "Violence Prevention Through Music" - RESTRICTED, 2001-2002; Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - FY 2002-2003 McEneny Legislative Local Initiative Grants, 2001-2004 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 2000 Legislative Local Initiative Request (Senator Joseph Bruno), 2001-2002; 2004; Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 2003 City of Albany Arts Grants Application, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - The Albany/Schenectady League of Arts Community Arts Connection 2002 Administrative Support Grant, Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 2003/2004 Albany County Youth Bureau Grant, 2002-2003; Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 2003 Tonko Legislative Initiative Grant (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 2004 City of Albany Arts Grants Application, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Letter to Assemblyman Paul Tonko About 2003 Legislative Delegation Grant (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 2003-2004 Legislative Local Initiative Grant Application (Senator Neil D. Breslin), Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - McEneny '02 Request and '03 Computer, 2003; Undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Special State Grant (Senator Joseph Bruno), 2003; Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - McEneny Final Report - Creative Music and Arts Program for Urban Children - RESTRICTED, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 2006 City of Albany Arts Grant Application, 2003-2005 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Delegation Grant for "Youth Care Provider Skills Enrichment Program", 2004 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Letter from New York State Council on the Arts Regarding Albany/Schenectady Decentralization Program Funding, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Albany/Schenectady League of Arts Informational and Community Arts Connection 2004 Grant, Undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - 2005 City of Albany Arts Grant Application, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - 2006 City of Albany Arts Grant Contract and Voucher, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - CDBG Consolidated Plan, 2005-2010; Undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - 2007 City of Albany Arts Grant, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - 2008 City of Albany Arts Grant Application, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Legislative Local Initiative Grant (Senator Bruno), 2006-2007; Undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Letters and Promotion for 'Living in My Neighborhood' Program (Senator Bruno), 2006-2007; Undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - 2007 Tonko Legislative Local Initiative Grant, 2006-2008 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - 2010 Legislative Member Grant (Assemblyman Tim Gordon), 2006; 2009-2010; Undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - CBDG Year 40 Application, 2006; 2014; Undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - CBDG Year 40 Letters of Support and Extra Forms, 2006; 2014; Undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Legislative Initiative Grant (Assemblyman Ron Canestrari), 2007 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - 2007 Albany County Youth Bureau Grant, Undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - 2007-2008 Legislative Local Initiative Grant Application (Senator Neil D. Breslin), Undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Community Youth Investment Grant, 2007; Undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Legislative Initiative Grant (Assembly Member Tim Gordon), 2007; Undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - McEneny 07 Request Archival Project, 2007; Undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - McEneny Legislative Initiative Grant Financial Through NYS Parks and Recreation, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Tonko Legislative Initiative Award, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Year 33 CDBG, 2007-2008; Undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - 2008 and 2009 City of Albany Arts Grant, 2007-2009 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - 2009 City of Albany Arts Grant, 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - 2008 Albany Youth County Bureau Grant, 2008-2009; Undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - City of Albany Arts Grant, 2008-2009; Undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Music Mobile CDBG 2009-2010 Year 35, 2008-2009; Undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - 2009 Albany County Youth Bureau Grant, 2008-2009; 2011; Undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - 2010 City of Albany Arts Grant, 2009-2010 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - CDBG Year 37 Letters of Support, 2009-2010 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 2010-2011 Legislative Initiative Grant (Assemblyman Jack McEneny), 2009-2010; Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - CDBG Year 37 Application and Letters of Support, 2009-2012 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 2010 Legislative Initiative Forms - George Amedore Research, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Research and Grant Application for Assemblyman Bob Reilly, 2010; Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Research and Request Form for Legislative Initiative Grant (Assemblyman James Tedisco), 2010; Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Senator Hugh Farley (44th) - Research, 2010; Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 2010 Albany County Youth Bureau Grant, 2010-2011; Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - OCFS Breslin 2009-2010 Final Report Materials, 2010-2011; Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - OCFS Senator Breslin 09-10 Application Materials, 2010-2011; Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 2010 City of Albany Arts Grant, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 2011 Albany County Regent for Proposals, Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Albany County Youth Bureau Grant, 2011; Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - CDBG Year 37 Contract, 2011; Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - CDBG Year 37 Contract and Revised Budget, 2011; Undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - CDBG Year 37 Voucher #1, 2011; Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - CDBG Year 37 Voucher #2, 2011-2012; Undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 2012 Albany County Youth Bureau Grant, 2011-2013 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - CDBG Year 39 Application, 2011-2013; 2015; Undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - 2012 City of Albany Arts Grant (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - CDBG Year 38 Revised Budget, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - CDBG Year 39 Support Letters, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - 2012 Legislative Local Initiative Grant Application, Undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - CDBG Year 38 Signed Contract, 2012; Undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - CDBG Year 38 Voucher #1, 2012-2013; Undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - 2013 City of Albany Arts Grant (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - CDBG Year 38 Voucher #2, 2013; Undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - CDBG Year 39 Signed Contract, 2013; Undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - CDBG Year 39 Voucher #1, 2013; Undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - 2014 Albany County Youth Bureau Grant, 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - 2014 City of Albany Arts Grant (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - CDBG Year 40 Signed Contract, 2014; Undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - CDBG Year 39 Voucher, 2014; Undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - CDBG Year 40 Voucher #1, 2014-2015 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - 2014 Albany County Youth Bureau Grant, 2014-2015; Undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - CDBG Year 41, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Materials for CDBG Year 41 Voucher #1, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Year 41 Community Development Block Grant Contract, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - CDBG Year 40 Voucher #2, 2015; Undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - CDBG Year 41 Voucher, 2015-2016 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - 2015 Albany County Youth Bureau Grant, 2015-2016; Undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - 2002 Community Art Connection Grant Operating Expense Budget Section, Undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - 2003 Albany/Schenectady League of Arts Community Arts Connection Grant Application and Guidelines, Undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - 2005 Community Arts Connection Grant Funding Information Booklet, Undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - 2010 City of Albany Arts Grant Application Increased Visibility Response, Undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Albany County Youth Bureau - Blank Forms, Undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Blank 2010-2011 Legislative Initiative Grant Forms (Canestrari), Undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Community Foundation Capacity Building Grant, Undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Handwritten Note for 1994 City of Albany Arts Commission Grant, Undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Incomplete Senator/Assembly Member Contact Sheet, Undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Music Mobile Meeting Schedule and Official Calendar for NYS Legislature, Undated (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - NYSCA Decentralization Program Brochure, Undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Research and Form for 2010-2011 Legislative Initiative Grant, Undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Special NYS Grants for Environmental Protection, Cultural and Recreational Programs Guidelines for FY 2002-2003 and FY 2005-2006, Undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Albany Housing Authority (AHA), 1986-2002; 3; 1.43 cubic ft.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  The Albany Housing Authority series contains materials from several music and other creative arts projects that took place in the housing projects that comprise the Albany Housing Authority: Ida Yarbrough Homes, Ezra Prentice Homes, and Corning Homes. The folders are largely titled by project name and housing project, save for separate yet related projects and extra material.
  - "Music In My Neighbor-hood" Notes Song Sheets, and Attendance Sheets -RESTRICTED, 1986; 1997; 1999; Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Various AHA Projects (1 of 2), 1992-1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Various AHA Projects (2 of 2), 1992-1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AHA Fall 93 Activity and Attendance Sheets, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Under One Sky" Project - RESTRICTED, 1993-1995; 1997; Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Promotion, Planning, and Grant Proposal for 95-96 Children's Songwriting and Self Esteem/'Parents for Kid' Programming (1 of 2), 1993-1996; Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Promotion, Planning, and Grant Proposal for 95-96 Children's Songwriting and Self Esteem/'Parents for Kid' Programming (2 of 2), 1993-1996; Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - AHA Fall Attendance Lists, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 94 AHA Activity and Attendance Sheets, 1994; Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 98 AHA Grant (1 of 2) - RESTRICTED, 1994-1996; 1998-1999; Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 98 AHA Grant (2 of 2) - RESTRICTED, 1994-1996; 1998-1999; Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Ezra Prentice Homes Song Sheets, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "It's My Community" Project-Ida Yarbrough Homes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Summer 95 AHA Attendance Lists - RESTRICTED, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Drawings By Desmond-Ezra Prentice Homes, 1995; Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Ida Yarbrough/Ezra Prentice Homes - Songwriting Project, 1995; Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Ida Yarbrough/Ezra Prentice Homes - Songwriting Project, 1995; Undated (Flat-file 1)
  - "If I Could Wish" Cassette Planning, Songwriting, and Children's Contributions, 1995; Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Materials for "Parent for Kids!" Songwriting Project for Interested Parents and Grant Materials, 1995; Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Parents for Kids Children's Songwriting and Self Esteem Project Notes and Correspondence, 1995; Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Song Ideas from Ida Yarbrough Homes, 1995; Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Song Ideas from Ida Yarbrough Homes, 1995; Undated (Flat-file 2)
  - Songwriting Worksheets from Ida Yarbrough Homes and Promotional Posters for Program at Ezra Prentice Boys and Girls Club, 1995; Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Attendance Sheets and Songwriting - Ida Yarbrough Homes, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Ezra Prentice Song Sheets and Cassette Recording Information, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "Neighbors Helping Neighbors" Songbook - Ezra Prentice Homes, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - "Neighbors Helping Neighbors" Songwriting Project - Ezra Prentice Homes, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - "Use of Your Head Today" Songbook - Ezra Prentice Homes, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Ezra Prentice Homes Attendance Sheets, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Rejected Illustrations for Songwriting Project - Ezra Prentice Homes, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Songwriting Project, Lyric Workshopping, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - "Use Your Hand Today" Songwriting Project - Ezra Prentice Housing and Others, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Writing and Editing Lyrics with Housing Residents, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Ida Yarbrough Lead Sheets, 1995; 1997; Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Corning Homes Songwriting Program Spring Attendance, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Songwriting Work for Various Songs, 1995-1997; Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Attendance Sheets, Chorus Sheets, and Song Lyrics - Ezra Prentice Homes, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - "I Miss You" Songbook - Ezra Prentice Homes, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - "If I Could Wish" Letters to Recording Participants and Lyric Workshopping for "Up the Hill", 1996 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Song sheets - "If I Could Wish", 1996 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - "Your Hands and My Hand's" Project - Corning Homes, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - "If I Could Wish" Project - Ida Yarbrough Homes, 1996; Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Originals - "If I Could Wish" Book, 1996; Undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Songbook Materials and Extra Drawings, 1996; Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Song Sheets and Drawings from Corning Homes, 1996; Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - "Your Hands and My Hands "Songbook - Corning Homes, 1996; Undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - "When I Do My Part" Project - Corning Homes, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Deleted Drawings, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - "I Miss You" Songwriting Project - Various Homes, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - "If I Could Wish" Children's Songwriting and Self Esteem Project Correspondence and Songwriting Drafts, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - 97 Press Release for Presentation/Distribution at Concerts, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Berkshire - Hudson Valley Chapter AOSA Presents: The Power to Connect - Interdisciplinary Projects for the Orff Schulwerk Program, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence that Accompanied "If I Could Wish" Cassette Deliveries, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Fax Transmittal About "If I Could Wish" Cassette and Songbook Distribution, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - "If I Could Wish" - Candy Deisley Feedback Letter, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - "If I Could Wish" Letter to be Distributed to Music Teachers and Sending List, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - "We Talked It Out" Songwriting Project - Corning Homes, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 55)